<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recents Article on Anthony Dellavecchia | Software Developer</title>
    <link>https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recents Article on Anthony Dellavecchia | Software Developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Magic Numbers</title>
      <link>https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/magic-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/magic-numbers/</guid>
      <description>Today, I got feedback from a code review and learned something new. It was about &amp;ldquo;magic numbers&amp;rdquo;, which are unique values with unexplained meaning or multiple occurrences which could (preferably) be replaced with named constants.
I&amp;rsquo;ve known about the concept of using constants rather than hard-coding values, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t think of that for &amp;ldquo;magic number&amp;rdquo; situations. It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty simple concept but I just wanted to share what I learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Never Miss Out on a Job Opening</title>
      <link>https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-never-miss-out-on-a-job-opening/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/how-to-never-miss-out-on-a-job-opening/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been disappointed to know that you got rejected from a job because you applied too late? They already hired someone else!
How many times have you missed out on job opportunities because you didn’t know a company was hiring for that position? It might be the perfect job for you, but you just didn’t know about it!
This script will keep you up to date with job postings so you never miss out on the right job opportunity!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Markdown</title>
      <link>https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/hugo-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.anthonydellavecchia.com/blog/hugo-markdown/</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of markdown examples, which also work with Hugo. (For my reference when adding markdown to future blog posts.)
This example Markdown file compliments of markdown-it.github.io
 h1 Heading 8-) h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Horizontal Rules    Typographic replacements Enable typographer option to see result.
(c) (C) (r) (R) (tm) (TM) (p) (P) +-
test.. test&amp;hellip; test&amp;hellip;.. test?&amp;hellip;.. test!&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
